Until this point, everything we've done has been
ここまでで データのロードと準備に関する作業を
related to loading and preparing the data.
すべて行ってきました
In this cell, we start actually building our deep neutral network.
このセルで実際に 深層ニューラルネットワークを構築していきます
First, we load TensorFlow.
まずはTensorFlowをロードします
Later we will use this EPOCHS variable,
後でこのエポック変数を使って
to tell TensorFlow how many times to run our training data through the network.
トレーニングデータをネットワーク経由で実行する回数をTensorFlowに指示します
In general, the more EPOCHS,
一般的に エポックが多ければ多いほど
the better our model will train,
モデルのトレーニングは向上しますが
but also the longer training will take.
トレーニング時間が長くなります
Later we'll also use the batch size variable,
後でバッチサイズ変数を使って
to tell TensorFlow, how many training images to run through the network at a time.
一度にネットワークを通過するトレーニング画像の数をTensorFlowに指示します
The larger the batch size,
バッチサイズが大きければ大きいほど
the faster our model will train,
モデルのトレーニングは速くなりますが
but our processor may have a memory limit on how large a batch it can run.
プロセッサーで実行できるバッチサイズにメモリー制限がある可能性があります
Now we come to LeNet,
ラボの中核をなす
which is the core of the lab.
LeNetを使用します
First we set more hyper parameters.
最初にハイパーパラメーターを設定します
In this case both hyper parameters relate to how we initialize our weights.
この場合 両方のハイパーパラメーターが 重みの初期化方法に関連します
You can experiment with these values and see if you can do better than what we have here.
これらの値は試すことができ ここで行うよりもっとうまくいくかどうかを確かめることができます
Then, we build the first convolutional layer.
次に 最初の畳み込み層を構築します
This layer has a five by five filter,
この層には
with an input depth of one,
5×5のフィルターがあり
and an output depth of six.
入力の深さは1 出力の深さは6です
We also initialize the bias,
また バイアスを初期化してから
then we use the conv2D function to convolve the filter over the images,
conv2D関数を使って画像にフィルターを畳み込み
and we add the bias at the end.
最後にバイアスを追加します
The formula for convolutions tells us that the output height equals,
畳み込みの公式では
the input height minus the filter height,
出力の高さ=(入力の高さ-フィルターの高さ+1)÷垂直方向の
plus one all divided by the vertical stride.
ストライドとなっています
In this case, that means 32, minus 5,
この例では
plus 2, all divided by 1, which equals 28.
(32-5+1)÷1=28です
The formula works the same way for the output width,
この式は 出力幅についても同様に機能します
which also equals 28.
出力幅も28です
So our convolutional layer output is 28 by 28 by 6.That's our first convolutional layer.
そのため 畳み込み層の出力は28×28×6です  これが最初の畳み込み層です
Next, we activate the output of the convolutional layer,
次に 畳み込み層の出力をアクティブにします
in this case with a ReLU activation function.
この例では ReLUアクティベーション関数を使います
Then we pool the output,
さらに 2x2のカーネルを
using the 2 by 2 kernel with a 2 by 2 stride,
2x2のストライドで出力をプールします
which gives us a pooling output of 14 by 14 by 6.
これにより 14x14x6のプーリング出力を得られます
The network then runs through another set of convolutional activation and pooling layers,
その後 ネットワークは 別の畳み込みアクティベーション層と プーリング層のセットを通過し
giving an output of 5 by 5 by 16.
5×5×16の出力を得られます
Then we flatten this output into a vector.
この出力を平坦化してベクターにします
The length of the vector is 5 times 5 times 16, which equals 400.
ベクターの長さは5×5×16 つまり400です
We pass this vector into a fully connected layer,
このベクターを
with a width of 120.
幅120の完全接続層に渡します
Then we apply a ReLU activation to the output of this fully connected layer.
その後 この完全接続層の出力にReLUアクティベーションを適用します
We repeat that pattern again this time with a layer width of 84.
今回は このパターンを層幅84で繰り返します
Finally, we attach a fully connected output layer,
最後に ラベルセットのクラス数に等しい幅で
with a width, equal to the number of classes in our label set.
完全接続出力層をアタッチします
In this case,we have 10 classes,
この場合 各桁に1つずつで
One for each digit,
クラスは10あるので
so the with the the output layer is 10.
出力層は10です
These outputs are also known as our logits,
これらの出力はロジットとしても知られています
which is what we return from the LeNet function.
これは LeNet関数から返されます
So that is the entire LeNet architecture.
これがLeNetのアーキテクチャー全体です
Now we just have to put it to use.
今度はこれを使用します